Guide to the Records of the Student Senators Council RG.44.0.1
New York University Archives
Records of the Student Senators Council
1974-2018
New York University Archives
New York University. Student Senators Council
RG.44.0.1
112.75 Linear Feet in 251 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 3 oversized shared flat boxes, and 1 shared cassette box
14 audiocassettes
The Student Senators Council (SSC) is an organization focused upon the interests, rights, and responsibilities of students. The SSC brings student concerns to the attention of the University Senate and appropriate university departments. The collection represents the different administrative aspects of the SSC including committees the SSC ran, events held by the SSC, and student resources. The Records of the Student Senators Council span from approximately 1974 to 2018. The collection contains memorandums, budgets, meeting minutes, correspondence, promotional materials, student handbooks, photographs, agendas, roll call lists, and directories.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into ten series and within each series, materials are organized first in chronological order and then in alphabetical order.
Series I: Administrative Files, 1974-2016
Series II: Committees and Boards, 1976-2015
Series III: Agendas and Minutes, 1975-2016
Series IV: Memos and Reports, 1976-2014
Series V: Governance and Policy, 1976-2012
Series VI: Events, 1976-2009
Series VII: Finance, 1978-2014
Series VIII: Membership, 1975-2018
Series IX: Student Resources, 1977-2015
Series X: Board of Trustees, 1981-1990
Historical Note
The New York University Student Senators Council (SSC) is part of the University Senate alongside the Administrators Management Council, Deans Council, Full-Time Continuing Contract Faculty Senators Council (C-FSC), and the Tenured/Tenure Track Faculty Senators Council (T-FSC); the latter two groups replaced the Faculty Senators Council, which was also originally affiliated with the SSC and University Senate. The SSC's 35 members consist of 23 student senators elected from the different schools at NYU and 12 student senators-at-large who are selected by other student senators. To ensure students always have a representative present at meetings, student senators are assigned an alternate in case of an absence.
The student senators are governed by the Senate Rules of Procedure, which are amended as needed. These rules outline members' responsibilities, meeting information, and committee information. According to the rules, the SSC's main function is to "be the representative body for all students at New York University, shall represent the students of New York University on the University Senate (Senate), and shall protect and promote the interests, rights, and responsibilities of students in all aspects of student life at the University."
The SSC is divided into numerous committees and each senator is required to participate in at least one. Non-SSC students are also invited to participate in the committees. The SSC's most significant committee, the University Committee on Student Life (UCSL), oversees student life on campus and is broken into smaller subcommittees such as the All Square Student Budget Allocation Committee (ASSABC), the Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), and the Student Activities Board (SAB).
In addition to the governing aspects of the University, the SSC is also involved in event planning, sponsoring events such as the Violet Ball and the All-University Games each year.
Sources: Student Senators Council Website: https://www.nyu.edu/about/leadership-university-administration/university-senate/membership/councils/student-senators-council.html Student Senators Council Rules of Procedure: https://www.nyu.edu/content/dam/nyu/stuSenatorsCouncil/documents/SSC%20Bylaws%205.8.14.pdf
Conditions Governing Access
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the New York University Archives, (212) 998-2646, university-archives@nyu.edu.
Series I: Administrative Files is closed for 20 years from the date of creation, with the exception of some materials housed in Box 159, which are protected under FERPA and are permanently closed.
Series II: Committees and Boards and Series VIII: Membership contain materials protected under FERPA and are permanently closed.
Series X: Board of Trustees, also housed in Box 159, are closed for 35 years from the date of creation.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Initial transfer of records from the Student Senators Council office in 2013 with the accession number 13.016. Additional accessions recieved in 2014 and 2019. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 2016.033 and 2019.022.
Scope and Content Note
The Records of the Student Senators Council consists of materials created and collected by the Student Senators Council (SSC) and University Council of Student Life (UCSL) from 1974 to 2018. Series I, III-V, VI, and X contain administrative papers, budgets, bylaws, constitutions, presentation notes, rules of procedures, resolutions, correspondence, memorandums, agendas, minutes, and reports, all of which provide in-depth insight regarding the ways in which the SSC and UCSL upheld the Council's mission to represent, protect, and promote the rights and interests of New York University students.
In order to become a member of the Student Senators Council, students from NYU's various schools were required to apply for a position within the SSC by submitting applications, resumes, personal statements, and in some cases, references. Series VIII: Membership contains materials relating to the recruitment of members such as completed applications, election materials, and advertisements; lists of selected Senators-at-Large and their alternates; committee preference sheets; and guidelines for selecting members.
The SSC oversaw numerous committees and boards, all of which are documented in Series II: Committees & Boards. This series mainly contains correspondence, administrative papers, some budgets, minutes, some audiocassette tapes, and memorandums -- all of which provide explanations about the work and goals of these groups, their roles within the New York University community, as well as their missions and values.
In addition to representing, protecting, and promoting the rights and interests of NYU students, the SSC prioritized the needs and wants of the student body by organizing social events throughout the academic year and providing various types of information guides. Series VI: Events provides details about social gatherings like books fairs, annual dinners and banquets for the student senators, the Violet Ball, and the All University Games through promotional materials, correspondence, photographs, administrative files, and invitations. Series IX: Student Resources contains directories, student handbooks, pamphlets with overviews about student government and SSC, guides to University services, as well as general information abyout NYU in the form of maps and recommendation lists.
Separated Materials
Issues of the "New York University Report," "The Courier: A Voice for Students at NYU," "the University," and "NYU Today" were removed from the Records of the Student Senators Council (RG.44.0.1) and transferred to the New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera (MC.334).
Correspondence.; Memorandums.; Agendas (administrative records); Student Government; Advertisements.; Handbooks.; Photographs.; Budgets.; Minutes (administrative records); Publications (documents); Constitutions.; Bylaws (administrative records); Resolutions (administrative records); Audiocassettes.; New York University. University Committee on Student Life; New York University. University Senate; New York University -- Students
- Series I: Administrative Files, 1974-2016; 13.73 Linear Feet in 27 manuscript boxes and 3 oversized shared flat boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Series I focuses on the general administrative function of the Student Senators Council and discusses issues such as academic year calendar changes and meeting schedules; internal emails between SSC members, UCSL members, and various committees and boards; materials regarding logistical information with regards to meetings and events;and administrative tasks. Materials in this series mainly consist of memorandum, calendars, correspondence, meeting minutes, and some certificates.
  Arrangement
  Materials are listed in chronological and alphabetical order.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Administrative records are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Box 159 contains restricted materials.
  - Creation of University Committee on Student Life (UCSL), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Establishment, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence to and from Non-Members, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Faculty and Course Evaluation School of Law, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Materials, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Polls of Student Opinion, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Senators-at-Large Ads for 1979-1980, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Student Senators Council - Certificates, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ARA Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Calendar, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Draft Resignation, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Evening Students, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Reading Speed, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Responsibilities of a St. Senator, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Senate Composition, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4, Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 9)
  - Times Modules, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - University Calendar, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Zabinsky's Resignation, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Allocation of SSC Seats: Guidelines, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Calendar, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Search, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Resignations: Maggin & Nicholas, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Responsibilities of a Senator-at-Large, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Summary of Senate Actions, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Brademas' Senate Address 12/10/81, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Student Matriculation Grievance (RESTRICTED), 1981 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Academic Calendar, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Activities Annex, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Allocation of SSC Seats: Guidelines, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Brademas' Speech: Carnegie Found, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Calendar for the Year, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Chairman's Remarks, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Chairman's Report - End of Year Summary, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Conference Room; Expanded Usage, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Convocation, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence non-SSC, UCSL, etc…, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Improved Communications with Admin, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Letters to the Editor, Washington Square News, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Library Hours, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Loeb Building Schedules 82-83, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Orientation Speech - Widman, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Personnel Information, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Responsibilities and Duties of a Student Senator, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Summary of Committees, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Summary of Senate Actions 80-81, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - General, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
  - Government Aid to Higher Education, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
  - Guest Seating at Meeting, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Student Conference on National Affairs, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Calendar Survey 4x4, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13, Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Non SSC, UCSL, etc…, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Deans of University, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Health Service Survey, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Meetings with the President, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Safety Forums, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Student Government Reference Numbers, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Student Leaders (non UCSL), 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - SUNY Conference at Buffalo, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Survey Results: Undergraduates Admitted '81, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - United Staff Association, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - University Calendar, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Brownstone News Magazine (RESTRICTED), 1983 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Meeting at Loeb Center, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - UCSL Sub Committee Assignments, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Communications Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Exit Interview Schedule, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - General, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
  - Housing Application Reviewed, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Ombudsman, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - University Calendar, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - University Government Structure, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Responsibilities of a Student Senator, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Voter Registration/New York Public Interest Research Group (NYPIRG), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Disabled Students Survey, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Health Center Survey, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Notes from Nick, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Student Services, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Administrator's Mailings, Benefits, Admin Management Council, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Availability Forms, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Calendar of Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Chancellor's Service Awards, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC only, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL only, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - SSC & UCSL Committees: Summary, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (Miscellaneous), 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Ruth Pengas Notebook, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Sample Packets & Originals, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Seville Hotel, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - South Africa, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Address by Dr. John Brademas - "New York University in the City", 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Availability Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Award for Patrick Kelly (Graduate Student Organization), 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Calendar of Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Sample Packets & Originals, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square News, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Availability Forms, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence from General Studies Program, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Council Contingency Funds (CCF) Request Forms, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Sample Packets & Originals, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Sample Packets for September & Blanks, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Senate Materials, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
  - SSC/USCL, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
  - Council Contingency Funds (CCF) Appeals, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Availability Forms, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Committee Preference Forms, members, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Materials, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
  - Sample Packets & Originals, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - SSC/USCL Committees: Summary, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Availability Forms (Blanks), 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Calendar of Meetings, SSC & UCSL versions, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Committee Preference Forms, non-members & summary of SSC/UCSL (Blanks) Comm., 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Committee Preference Forms, SSC (Blanks), 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Committee Preference Forms, UCSL (Blanks), 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Committees: Summary, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Sample Packets & Blanks for September, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Sample Packets & Originals, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Meeting Materials, 1990, 1997, 2004-2011 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Disciplinary Hearing (RESTRICTED), 1991 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Senators-at-Large for A/Y 1991-1992 (SSC Advertisements from the Washington Square News) (Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Papers, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 22, Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Availability Forms, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Calendar, SSC & UCSL Versions, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Committee Preference Forms (SSC), 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Committee Preference Forms (UCSL), 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Committee Preference Forms & Summary (non-members), 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Inquiries from the Student Body, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Sample Packets & Blanks for September, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Sample Packets & Originals, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Student Information System, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Washington Square News, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square News (Advertisements for Senators-at-Large), 1991-1993 (Box Shared University Archives 147, Folder 7)
  - Availability Forms, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Calendar of Meetings (SSC & UCSL versions), 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Calendars, SSC & UCSL versions, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Committee Preference Forms (SSC), 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Committee Preference Forms (UCSL), 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Committee Preference Forms & Summary (for alternates and non-members), 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Inquiries from the Student Body, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Religious Holidays, Policy, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Sample Packets & Blanks for September, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Sample Packets & Originals, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Senate Materials, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
  - SSC/UCSL Committees: Summary, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Student Services, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6, Box 11, Folder 1)
  - All University Calendar of Events, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Availability Forms (Blanks), 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bookstore, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Calendar of Meetings, SSC & UCSL versions, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Calendars, SSC & UCSL versions, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Committee Descriptions: SSC & UCSL, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Committee Preference Forms (SSC), 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Committee Preference Forms (UCSL), 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Committee Preference Forms & Summary (for Alternates & Non-members), 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Forum, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Information Session, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Inquiries from the Student Body, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Religious Holidays, Policy, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Ruth's Alumni/Student Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Sample Packets & Blanks for September, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Senate Materials, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 19, Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - SSC/UCSL Committees: Summary, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Student Employment, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Availability Forms (Blanks), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Calendar of Meetings, SSC & UCSL versions, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Calendars, SSC & UCSL versions, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Committee Descriptions: Senate, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Committee Description: SSC/UCSL, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Committee Preference & Description (Student Body Alternates), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Committee Preference Forms, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Committee Preference Forms (SSC), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Committee Preference Forms (UCSL), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Committee Preference Forms & Summary (for Alternates & Non-members), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Inquiries from the Student Body, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Rules & Organization, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Sample Packets & Blanks for September, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Sample Packets & Originals, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - SSC/UCSL Committees: Summary, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Alternate Senators (at-Large), 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Calendar of Meetings, 2 Versions SSC & UCSL, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Committee Chairs, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Committee Description (Senate), 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Committee Description (SSC & UCSL), 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - General Information, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Student Guide to NYU, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Calendar of Meetings, 2 Versions SSC & UCSL, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Committee Description: Senate, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Committee Description: SSC/UCSL, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day/Government Relations, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
  - Flier Distribution List (Deans), 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - General Information, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Religious Holidays, University Policy, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Sample Packets, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Calendar of Meetings, 2 Versions SSC & UCSL, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Committee Descriptions: Senate, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Committee Descriptions: SSC/UCSL, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)